simplyaudiobooks.com 2004-12-08

# Simply Audiobooks - North America's Audio Book Rental Company

Please take a minute to read the following policy so you understand how we use the personal information we ask you to submit. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. If you use any of Simply Audiobooks' services, you agree to these terms.

* * *

**Background**

When you register at Simply Audiobooks, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your orders and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you newsletters you are subscribed to during registration, as well as messages about Simply Audiobooks special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. Occasionally, we send our customers special offers and promotional information via postal mail, using the shipping address provided.

* * *

**Collection and Use of Information**

When you first register at Simply Audiobooks, we ask for your email address and a password. When you place your first order for the Simply Audiobooks Service, we ask you for your full name, physical address, telephone number and credit card number so we can ship your order. We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue, not for marketing purposes. You must certify that you are at least 18 years old. (People under 18 cannot use Simply Audiobooks's services.)

Email address information entered by prospective customers will not be disclosed to 3rd parties without prior approval by the customer. Simply Audiobooks may use email addresses entered by prospective customers for occasional informational mailings. Simply Audiobooks respects and complies with all federal anti-spam regulations and any recipient may unsubscribe from any email list at any time.

Our server stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to Your Account and make the appropriate changes. You must be signed in to access Your Account.

Simply Audiobooks also offers an Affiliate program, where affiliate members direct customers to Simply Audiobooks through links on their Web sites. We ask affiliates for their site name (URL), mailing address, primary contact, pay-to address, technical contact, and other site-related information to determine whether a site will be included in our Affiliate Network. You can email us at info@simplyaudiobooks.com for more details. The information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for that program; none of this information is used for general marketing purposes.

We also track your order and billing history so you can access Your Account and immediately determine which CDs you've rented and how you paid for them. This information is also used to remove rented titles from your recommendations list.

* * *

**Viewing and Updating Your Information on Simply Audiobooks**

You can always access the personal information you have provided to Simply Audiobooks by going to Your Account. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime.

* * *

**Disclosure**

Except as described in this section, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personally identifying information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared.

We occasionally use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services necessary to our operations. For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our Web pages, process credit card transactions, analyze customers' interaction with our site and process consumer surveys. We also provide postal addresses to the Post Office for delivery purposes. In the course of providing such services, these companies may have to contact with your personal identifying information. By contractual agreement, these companies must treat your information in accordance with this Policy. We will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our users. In conjunction with these partners, we occasionally send promotional announcements to particular customers. We do not automatically include our users in any particular marketing promotion; instead, we use a variety of factors, including user activity at the Simply Audiobooks site, to determine the appropriate users. You can call and request that your name be excluded from these mailings with our marketing partners. We may use a vendor to carry out these mailings. However, the partner company never sees your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly.

Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission. Simply Audiobooks also reserves the right to disclose information when required by law.

We also provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We do this so that we and our advertisers can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you first-rate services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our customers. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific users.

Customers should check back for updates to this policy. Simply Audiobooks will obtain email consent from any user if the company is going to be using the information collected in a manner different from that stated when the user registered.

* * *

**Security and Access**

For transmitting your personal information to us, we use a secure server (SSL), which encrypts all of your personal information. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.

You can access Your Account from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit cards, and mailing list preferences. Please note that you must be signed in to Simply Audiobooks to access this information.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

* * *

**Contact**

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact [privacy@simplyaudiobooks.com](mailto:privacy@simplyaudiobooks.com).

* * *

_Last updated August 2003 (c) Simply Audiobooks, Inc._
